And then a shaker.
Time-stamped.
Poke at it.
Poke a little. Poke a little each.
Wrap it around and poke it.
Hey can see
(of an unmarried couple) be close
boot up (computer)
That's what we'll be discussing today.
mornings
Let's talk about what we're gonna do on our last day.
And then maybe
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
That's four more of these USBs over here.
It's possible that what's this? What's this?
This hard drive.
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
In the morning I think the main discussion was
And then there's nothing else to do while the discussion is going on
If people are in deep thought
It's an embarrassment.
You can give this a go.
Now that's embarrassing.
No, no, no.
Let's take it apart and see what it is.
Wow.
Only four?
For only four.
No, it's fine.
You've taken this apart for me, right? I'll do it.
Because you're right.
Haha I've already installed this thing
If you need a rechargeable battery, you can get it here. Thank you.
fastener
It's out.
What can we do?
Keep the box.
Well, this thing inside can be thrown away.
this category of ingredients
It hasn't flowed in the last two years.
Then 1% first.
This one's for when everyone's in deep thought.
I can tell you about this one.
What is this thing?
In fact, you can look at this place
interjection of surprise
That's you looking at my workshop.
Are we breaking and entering?
workplace
And there are six computers in this place, right?
Uh, and then 77.
Eight. - Uh-huh.
Recording will be this computer.
Each computer corresponds to one of your eyes.
One eyeglass.
And then this every computer I have every time you guys uh
End of recording.
Every three hours.
And then it's gonna be, uh-
That's where it's dumped into this hard drive.
And then this hard drive
It's the hard drive you'll be installing later.
Let's say it's this.
This L1, this L1.
This L2, this
All the names are written here.
All right, here's your data in this.
It's our second life.
Haha Second Life is in this one
Uh, let's say I'm an L1, right?
And then when you're done.
That's what's gonna stick this eye up here.
And in the meantime, I've been following this.
The first hard drive.
Yeah, and then this hard drive, it's got two cables.
One for the computer.
One for the power supply.
And then this power supply
It's for this hard drive to pretend it's on the computer.
So what this box means is that
He gives a simulation of a computer environment
cheat sb again
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so the hard drive knows it's got to work.
Uh and then this line ah this line
We've had some fun wiring it up.
Growing up like this is a hanging
What happens if the power goes out suddenly?
It's not good to say that a sudden computer blackout is going to
There's no such thing as a USB.
It's one of those backup power supplies.
desirable
Beijing Providence
(express) thanks
we
Can we just talk and pretend?
Yeah, or maybe you guys should bring it first.
What did you bring?
You brought it.
You'd better put on your glasses.
These glasses.
Well, it doesn't cover it.
I don't think it's even covered.
It's not covered now.
He's got a hole right here.
And then this place is going to be packed in here
So that's how you want it to be aligned.
Then slowly push it in.
Let's see how it goes.
It's a little lighter.
That student told me the other day that it's quite fragile.
How do you do that?
It's okay.
Isn't there an opening here?
It's the opposite of this one.
You just put them like this against
Then we'll see how it goes.
Push that in your hand.
He's still a little tight here if you put a little pressure on him.
But don't break it if you try too hard.
It's like you're so fragile.
But I don't really know much about this
There's a lot of screws to be screwed.
Yeah, where's the screw?
In there.
Oh, I see.
easy
And then just put it in.
Uh-huh.
And then we're gonna put it in this box.
It's just that you'd better take this place off
And then this movie can be discarded.
Because we're going to use it for screws later.
Is it just four screws?
Uh, eight.
Eight? - Yeah.
yea
That's you. You pull out that strip.
Yeah, and then you see that hole?
The long one.
He's got a screw hole in there.
You're gonna have to put that on, too.
That's the screw hole for the big screw.
Ah which one?
Uh, I've got one screw up here.
That's it.
This thing.
Well, how about I point you in the right direction?
Hey, you're on the right track.
Uh-huh.
And then every one of them over here.