And then a shaker.
Time-stamped.
Poke at it.
Poke a little. Poke a little each.
Wrap it around and poke it.
Hey can see
(of an unmarried couple) be close
boot up (computer)
That's what we'll be discussing today.
mornings
Let's talk about what we're gonna do on our last day.
And then maybe
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
That's four more of these USBs over here.
It's possible that what's this? What's this?
This hard drive.
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
In the morning I think the main discussion was
And then there's nothing else to do while the discussion is going on
If people are in deep thought
It's an embarrassment.
You can give this a go.
Now that's embarrassing.
No, no, no.
Let's take it apart and see what it is.
Wow.
Only four?
For only four.
No, it's fine.
You've taken this apart for me, right? I'll do it.
Because you're right.
Haha I've already installed this thing
If you need a rechargeable battery, you can get it here. Thank you.
fastener
It's out.
What can we do?
Keep the box.
Well, this thing inside can be thrown away.
this category of ingredients
It hasn't flowed in the last two years.
Then 1% first.
This one's for when everyone's in deep thought.
I can tell you about this one.
What is this thing?
In fact, you can look at this place
interjection of surprise
That's you looking at my workshop.
Are we breaking and entering?
workplace
And there are six computers in this place, right?
Uh, and then 77.
Eight. - Uh-huh.
Recording will be this computer.
Each computer corresponds to one of your eyes.
One eyeglass.
And then this every computer I have every time you guys uh
End of recording.
Every three hours.
And then it's gonna be, uh-
That's where it's dumped into this hard drive.
And then this hard drive
It's the hard drive you'll be installing later.
Let's say it's this.
This L1, this L1.
This L2, this
All the names are written here.
All right, here's your data in this.
It's our second life.
Haha Second Life is in this one
Uh, let's say I'm an L1, right?
And then when you're done.
That's what's gonna stick this eye up here.
And in the meantime, I've been following this.
The first hard drive.
Yeah, and then this hard drive, it's got two cables.
One for the computer.
One for the power supply.
And then this power supply
It's for this hard drive to pretend it's on the computer.
So what this box means is that
He gives a simulation of a computer environment
cheat sb again
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so the hard drive knows it's got to work.
Uh and then this line ah this line
We've had some fun wiring it up.
Growing up like this is a hanging
What happens if the power goes out suddenly?
It's not good to say that a sudden computer blackout is going to
There's no such thing as a USB.
It's one of those backup power supplies.
desirable
Beijing Providence
(express) thanks
we
Can we just talk and pretend?
Yeah, or maybe you guys should bring it first.
What did you bring?
You brought it.
You'd better put on your glasses.
These glasses.
Well, it doesn't cover it.
I don't think it's even covered.
It's not covered now.
He's got a hole right here.
And then this place is going to be packed in here
So that's how you want it to be aligned.
Then slowly push it in.
Let's see how it goes.
It's a little lighter.
That student told me the other day that it's quite fragile.
How do you do that?
It's okay.
Isn't there an opening here?
It's the opposite of this one.
You just put them like this against
Then we'll see how it goes.
Push that in your hand.
He's still a little tight here if you put a little pressure on him.
But don't break it if you try too hard.
It's like you're so fragile.
But I don't really know much about this
There's a lot of screws to be screwed.
Yeah, where's the screw?
In there.
Oh, I see.
easy
And then just put it in.
Uh-huh.
And then we're gonna put it in this box.
It's just that you'd better take this place off
And then this movie can be discarded.
Because we're going to use it for screws later.
Is it just four screws?
Uh, eight.
Eight? - Yeah.
yea
That's you. You pull out that strip.
Yeah, and then you see that hole?
The long one.
He's got a screw hole in there.
You're gonna have to put that on, too.
That's the screw hole for the big screw.
Ah which one?
Uh, I've got one screw up here.
That's it.
This thing.
Well, how about I point you in the right direction?
Hey, you're on the right track.
Uh-huh.
And then every one of them over here.
And then this one too. So that's eight.
Yeah, I got it.
See, that's the big screw.
You see this?
For small screws
Come here.
Inside, you just stick it in, right?
Just that, uh, that.
right
Well, it's supposed to go in there.
Sub-formed circuits or what?
We've been complaining about the magnetism for the last time
But it seems like nobody has anything today.
Everyone seems to be taking it well today.
To what?
The one that comes with it can't give you anything.
It's just that this screwdriver is not magnetic.
Yeah, that's why it's a big deal here.
It's numb when you put the screws in.
That's where it's enlarged.
But the big ones will snap in.
Uh, that's what he looks like.
There's nothing he can do.
Right through this hole.
You just have to fix it like this.
This one? - Yeah.
Or stuff it inside.
I stuffed a little lens.
It should be as long as it takes to hold it in place
Is that right?
better
we
Is it possible to have a little BGM support to
What kind of music do people listen to?
I'm listening to David Tao.
Uh, rm rm rm.
I'm an omega so I'm just listening.
Give everyone a more energized
Look at that Northeast Sister Li's BGM
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
This is the kind of work that must be done with a lot of energy.
I want to carry it. - Carry it.
(onom.) hahaha
It's just a half-embedded one, isn't it? That's good.
OK, my hometown in the Northeast.
I'm Inari.
No, not that Changchun
Changchun, Jilin Province
Do you know this city?
Did you know there's a Jilin City in Jilin Province?
I'm not in Changchun.
seems like
the Great Northeast
Blowing out beautiful patterns
I'll give you two for each song you play together.
Drunken moon warms my heart
The Great Northeast is my hometown
Gee, why do humans like to listen to music like that?
Confusing behavior
And then there's a screw over here looking at the side
It looks like it's okay out here without putting it back in.
I think we threw out this one the other night.
I remember this outfit.
You can throw this one away, right?
I managed to put it in yesterday.
Oh, I see. Well, we'll do it that day.
Is that all right?
It's ready to go in.
Yes, I've already been in.
Ah, you've been there.
I think those wiring ones at our university
Soldering the boards is no different than going in.
In particular, electricity
Uh, electrician to electrician, weld plate to electrician.
The internship will do some amazing stuff
Our school, too.
You know why we softwares have to learn it too.
Next assembly line
Are you hooked up to a computer on the next assembly line?
(onom.) hahaha
The next one needs a senior technician
Hahaha advanced technician pause
noisy
3,000 Jeet Kune Do to 5,000 Jeet Kune Do.
Do you think this is Jeet Kune Do?
What is Jeet Kune Do?
skilled worker
Hey why am I
Because you pressed it the other way around.
Ah, hi, hi.
It's over. It's embarrassing.
Chatting away at the bottom of the pile.
Hahaha no I have to fight for it
I can't be at the bottom of the list.
Ha-ha-ha.
You're done, and then what?
Don't you have to do anything?
It should be fine after the screwing.
And he's just going to blithely say it's done.
And then?
He provoked me.
What the hell are the chances?
Is that so?
I think so.
All right.
You see, you're not pretending to be beautiful.
I don't need to load it.
I'll do it with or without the strip.
It's a pain in the ass not to install it.
You can put bars in it.
If it needs to be installed.
And then just load it yourself more often haha
OK
He's ready to go.
Completed a strange first mission
And then this EGO life last day
Who will people invite?
final day
The last day is Sunday, right?
Sunday.
Sunday afternoon.
Ah, who will everyone invite?
How many people will be invited?
You guys write on the blackboard.
You can write on the board.
Come on, I've got a very nice handwriting.
We also have a shelf.
Why don't we print them too?
What frame?
Black chalkboard stand yes?
If you think this is hard to write like this
Well, there's actually a
No pen.
Let's wait to install it.
Write first. It's not a problem.
It doesn't affect me as a calligrapher.
Where's the pen? Where's the pen?
good question
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
Ask him about AIB.
Looking for my iPhone?
(onom.) hahaha
Looking for my
Looking for my Pansu.
We're all iPhones, aren't we?
Seems like I should be the iPhone.
Oops what kind of crap ah hahaha
Ah, is that a dog?
Why didn't I change it?
He's an iPhone. He's Izzy.
Oh, oh, OK.
Hey so our one person in the end which two ah
Me too. - Hey, you too. - Yeah.
I'm - I'm - I'm - I'm - I'm - I'm not - OK.
hahaha ah oh so hey that lol
We're going to start with one or two.
Hey, what about us?
Ah OK yesterday I didn't
I didn't guess yesterday.
Though I guessed he might be a skeptic EGO life.
Last day's list
you
hips
That's what it says.
waist of a brush stroke
How do you spell waist?
That's what it says.
classifier for objects in rows such as words
Dumb ass didn't remove the clamps.
Ha ha ha ah
Why didn't you unload it?
Bao Gui Tou Bao Gui Tou
Hahaha okay
first place
Let's just say you invite a few people
I'll invite one.
Asa Asa invited one ah
I'm not sure because we're so far away.
I don't know if my buddy's gonna make it.
And your studio.
I'll invite one.
Shallow invites one
What's the name?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hahaha this one's not gonna work.
I'm just gonna put a straight face on it, that's all.
Ah, it's good to have a straight face.
Or you use that little ball.
I guess it's enough to draw a little person.
That's what boys do.
Girls twice.
You invited hahaha is this the girl you invited?
Ah you ah then I also invite a girl
This one, this braid.
He doesn't have this connector on his head.
Ah this wig my goodness
Ha ha ha ha! Let's go to the sky!
Hey I should invite a boy
Boys.
I love the three legs of the heart hahahahaha this fits right in
I'm sorry for drawing my head by accident.
Ha ha ha ha ha OK
I could actually ask a girl
But I'm not sure he'll be able to handle it.
Because he's pretty far away.
Hahaha ok doubtful right doubtful
There's more.
I can put a name under each one.
Write a host for him.
Host?
Well, your address is your code name.
Claim it.
No, no, no.
You'll just write underneath this little man
Or write one on it or on your face or something.
Whose is this?
So, he's stupid. He's stupid.
Hahaha!
This is Woo-hin's.
That says LX LYX
(onom.) hahahaha
Who does this one belong to?
I'm Lucy or I'll write an "l".
Ha-ha Lucy.
And you're inviting two, right?
Yeah, but one of them might not make it.
Both genders are female huh?
I don't know if I can make it.
Just draw me a star. A pentagram.
OK
Now we have one, two, three, four, five, six, six guests.
Uh, 4-6 guests.
right
4-6 guests 4-6 guests OK
hiccup
We were going to do it if we could.
Go and invite the people around you.
Ah yes.
Or a novel.
Is it by knocking on doors and asking questions?
hiccup
It's better to carry a basket of eggs.
Ha ha ha ha eat shit
if if if
that is, if
They can give out eggs if they come.
What sounds like a sausage.
Ha ha ha! Tomorrow our land will be reported.
Hahaha we can get a cop shot tomorrow
(onom.) hahaha
2 Invite neighbors
It's hard to write the word "waist
Or you can be crooked.
I think so.
Bring a lanyard.
I'll give you this column if you come.
If you don't come, I won't send you.
haha neighbor (polite address)
be at a standstill
curse it!
Qi Wan Shi was in tears.
It's got a vintage feel to it.
This is our plan to question the plan.
So many question marks.
We're like the Riddler.
(onom.) hahahaha
the Riddler
And then we also
And what else?
Uh, this is the personnel section.
Uh, the crew.
There are still five people in the crew.
In total, look.
How many people do we end up holding?
And then look at this activity
What's the point of adding this number?
filament
Isn't it okay to get technical?
How much trouble did you get into later?
Okay, so one, two, three, four.
Four to six four plus five five
It's 9+5, 9999 to 11.
9 to 11, then each.
private saving of family members
Count us in, right?
Hey, thanks, too.
9-11 Figure positive infinity
Because we can invite the neighbors
It's very strict, isn't it?
right
It's not exactly infinity, is it? 1.6 billion.
Hahaha now our country
Our population of 1.6 billion?
1414, right? Then it's 14 and done.
That's half a million dollars for the move.
91 iPhone haha
Does it fit? Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
And then the good people identified
This is the first.
Three dots below the third of the first big dot.
And then we have a second point.
Shall we start the content part of the program? - Yes.
I think it's a tough nut to crack.
We'll be chewing for a long time.
So we're just gonna start with this?
Is there anything else?
(onom.) hahaha
Activities
Think about it.
I think I remember people filling out the questionnaire.
Right? - Yeah.
What did everyone fill out on the questionnaire?
It's not all GPT-generated, is it?
No. Ha ha ha.
I thought of the GPT generation myself
Well, since we're talking about Hunan GPT.
So let's start with
LYX, come here.
Hahaha I I think that's the one that's uh 7 days
Then buy the flowers for me.
And then a vase each.
Then it's the equivalent of uh, waking up and spending a day or two.
And then it just happens to be a cycle.
It's just that you can let this flower open slowly
Then take the petals of this flower
And then make that embossing.
Then it's more environmentally friendly
Make it one of those postcards.
And got that acrylic glass.
And then it's embedded.
It's the kind of handmade that looks better
And then it's also about plants.
And then the raw materials were carefully raised by themselves for another 7 days
Then again, it felt like forming a mural
Just did some peripheral
We can distribute them on that day.
be on top of sb's game
Where's the tweed?
The flowers are still waking up.
Because I look at me.
I was just thinking about planting one of those things
It's the kind of world that fits the Earth.
The Earth's discovery is basically impossible to germinate in 7 days.
And then I thought about what kind of talent I'd buy for these flowers.
The flowers from Yunnan that were sent directly by HSBC are
I think he has two buns.
Yes I bought peony ah really do not want to give away
sound of child's crying
I've got some flowers that will open in the next couple of days.
You want to find some scissors or something?
Scissors to dry
Or do we have to finish cracking the back?
Uh, do it first. Do it first.
Where are the scissors?
I've bought several bunches.
The scissors are here and I bought carnations to write with.
It just so happens that we have more girls.
Ah, that too.
The petals can be used for embossing.
And then I bought the embosser to see what kind of dryer it was.
What's this?
This is a flower. This one needs to be nurtured.
Is this a peony?
Well, I bought more than I realized.
He said it would take a day or two to bloom
It takes two or three days to press the flowers.
And then this one for two or three days.
What kind of lily is this?
Vanilla or something.
What lily? - The lily of the valley.
Nutrients soaked in water to speed up the wake-up call.
These two colors of
One white and one yellow.
Is it a package?
I think I remember him sending two packages.
Why don't you see if we can do a talent show?
See which ones are yours.
Without me.
Without you.
Put it on the ground first.
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
Did you guys buy anything?
Not yet. Not yet. Buy some more.
a pug
Haha, bring the money into the group.
Look at this. It's all there.
And then?
And then it's vase gesticulation, gesticulation, gesticulation, gesticulation.
Is there any kind of formality to it?
The format is one for each of the six of us
I got the vase, too.
Then we'll all divide the flowers.
I've kept it for a day or two or three after I split it.
Uh, he's gonna open it up a little bit.
When it opens, use these petals.
or
I've seen them embossed by just taking this bloom.
Cut out the flowers.
And then just press him like this.
It's going to be one of those flat
And then the flower that unfolded
And then it can be done in the kind of postcard
The kind of postcard greeting cards I buy
And that one, including what's the name of that one.
That acrylic double glazing
And then it's like one of those picture frames.
You can give it to someone else.
And then some leaves and stuff.
And then it was like.
Don't you have that outdoor program?
We can then pick up some leaves
And then just put it together like a picture.
Yes and then bookmarks too
And then we'll all just make our own.
And then the last day.
Because I want this form
Just invite all your best friends and stuff.
You can make your own. You can raise your own.
And then it would be nice to hand them out to everyone.
And it's more in line with the seven-day cycle.
Then I thought I'd wake him up first.
Yeah, you can.
I'm sure I'll wake him up today.
Next in line
Who's next?
I'll do this next.
The next Lulua student.
I'm here for the game.
It's actually my idea.
It's also about DIY.
For me I just I thought at first that it was possible to
Because it's World Earth Day.
So I thought I'd just do something a little more eco-friendly.
I don't know if you've ever done a jellyfish light.
It's just been a couple years since it's been on the scene.
Uh, it's a little light that looks like a jellyfish.
right
And then this thing it originally came with a kit.
That is, you can just buy the kit online and do it
But that's what I'm thinking.
That is, since it's World Earth Day.
I've brushed up on a tutorial before
You can use the lid of that tea cup.
Then use it as a subject
Then it's time to add some more ribbon
Or beads or something.
Uh, I didn't know we had one here.
No hot glue gun
If not.
We'll see if there's an alternative.
Or maybe it's okay to buy one.
And then it's all together.
Just about everyone makes one of these little lamps
It's just that he's kinda good looking.
And then this is one of the scenarios
There's another one that's also a little bit of this
How can I put it?
Low-carbon and recycled
That is, has anyone ever made a cardboard puppy
The one that was so hot the other day.
Yeah, and then you can put it on the doorstep.
And then the good thing about cardboard puppies is
If you want to do it very simply
Just take a cardboard box and cut it up.
Then just draw a little dog head and stick it on.
If you want to get a little more complicated
There are just a few.
It's just that if it's complicated, you'll need to cut more than one.
And then make a big
I've seen someone do a Doberman before.
But I've never done that.
Just but just read the tutorial
Seems pretty easy too.
It's easy to cut out just by drawing the cardstock
This I think.
So I think this is a good idea for
I was thinking the same thing.
There's gonna be a lot of cardboard boxes around here.
If that's all it takes